arfitech.com 2018-12-29

# Arnim IT Privacy Policy

#### Arnim IT Respects Your Privacy

At Arnim IT we recognize that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use Arnim IT services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

Arnim IT Corporations customers information including personal contact information and server data is treated with strict confidentiality and will not be shared except in the limited circumstances outlined in this policy. Arnim IT adheres to the U.S.-EU and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework and the principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement. Arnim IT regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy.

Arnim IT Corporation collects cookies on our Web site to capture information about page visits. This information is anonymous and we use this information only internally to improve the content we provide to our visitors. Information from the cookies is used to gauge page popularity, analyze traffic patterns on our site and guide development of other improvements to our site. If you choose to communicate to us and provide personally identifiable information about yourself, we will use this information only to respond to your inquiry. We will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose that information to third parties unless required to do so by law or in circumstances outlined in this policy.

#### Information Collection

Users may voluntarily provide Arnim IT their contact information including, but not limited to, email address, name, phone, address, zip code and other personally identifiable information. This information will be used by Arnim IT to respond to user inquiries and provide follow up communications. Examples of areas where users may voluntarily submit contact information to Arnim IT include, but are not limited to: product orders, newsletter sign-up, emails to Arnim IT,, help desk tickets . Users may opt-out, modify or delete their personal information by sending an email to cs@arnimit.com, 

#### Information Sharing

Arnim IT only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Arnim IT in the following limited circumstances: We have your consent. We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to: 

  * (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, 
  * (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, 
  * (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or 
  * (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Arnim IT, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

Per our agreement with the Internet Corporation of Assigned Names and Numbers (ICANN) and American Registry for Internet Numbers (ARIN), we must add valid contact information for each domain name and IP you register. It is possible to purchase Private Registration by requesting it from your salesperson at the time of your order. By using private registration you can hide your personal contact information and display proxy information instead. Private Registration is available for many domain name extensions. However, some registries do not allow it
